Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1964 -- 2020; UA003.003; 23.3 Linear Feet; 48 Digital Object(s) 48 zip files containing 1,974 files.; 3.97 Gigabytes
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1964 -- 1981; UA003.003.002
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 15, 1981; UA003.003.067.00004 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 15, 1981; UA003.003.067.00005 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 13, 1981; UA003.003.067.00006 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 30, 1981; UA003.003.067.00007 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 16, 1981; UA003.003.067.00008 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 21, 1981; UA003.003.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Working Papers, 1981 -- 2000; UA003.003.003
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 18, 1981; UA003.003.067.00010 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 17, 1982; UA003.003.067.00011 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 17, 1982; UA003.003.067.00012 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 21, 1982; UA003.003.067.00013 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 21, 1982; UA003.003.067.00014 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 21, 1982; UA003.003.067.00015 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 19, 1982; UA003.003.067.00016 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 28, 1982; UA003.003.067.00017 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 20, 1982; UA003.003.067.00018 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 20, 1982; UA003.003.067.00019 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 17, 1982; UA003.003.067.00020 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, December 15, 1982; UA003.003.067.00021 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 16, 1983; UA003.003.067.00022 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, January 12, 1983; UA003.003.067.00023 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 16, 1983; UA003.003.067.00024 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1983; UA003.003.067.00025 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1983; UA003.003.067.00026 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1983; UA003.003.067.00027 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1983; UA003.003.067.00028 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 18, 1983; UA003.003.067.00029 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 28, 1983; UA003.003.067.00030 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 21, 1983; UA003.003.067.00031 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 19, 1983; UA003.003.067.00032 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 19, 1983; UA003.003.067.00033 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 16, 1983; UA003.003.067.00034 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 15, 1984; UA003.003.067.00035 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.067.00036 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.067.00037 (Box 67)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.068.00001 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.068.00002 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.068.00003 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.068.00004 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 18, 1984; UA003.003.068.00005 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 16, 1984; UA003.003.068.00006 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 16, 1984; UA003.003.068.00007 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee (August 1984), UA003.003.068.00008 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 19, 1984; UA003.003.068.00009 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 17, 1984; UA003.003.068.00010 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 15, 1984; UA003.003.068.00011 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, January 16, 1985; UA003.003.068.00012 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 20, 1985; UA003.003.068.00013 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 17, 1985; UA003.003.068.00014 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 17, 1985; UA003.003.068.00015 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 17, 1985; UA003.003.068.00016 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 17, 1985; UA003.003.068.00017 (Box 68)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 20, 1985; UA003.003.069.00001 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 17, 1985; UA003.003.069.00002 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 15, 1985; UA003.003.069.00003 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 15, 1985; UA003.003.069.00004 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 16, 1985; UA003.003.069.00005 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 14, 1985; UA003.003.069.00006 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 14, 1985; UA003.003.069.00007 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 14, 1985; UA003.003.069.00008 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, December 18, 1985; UA003.003.069.00009 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 19, 1986; UA003.003.069.00010 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 19, 1986; UA003.003.069.00011 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 16, 1986; UA003.003.069.00012 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 16, 1986; UA003.003.069.00013 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 16, 1986; UA003.003.069.00014 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 22, 1986; UA003.003.069.00015 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 16, 1986; UA003.003.069.00016 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 16, 1986; UA003.003.069.00017 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 14, 1986; UA003.003.069.00018 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 14, 1986; UA003.003.069.00019 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 17, 1986; UA003.003.069.00020 (Box 69)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, Working Papers, October 15, 1986; UA003.003.070.00001 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 15, 1986; UA003.003.070.00002 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 15, 1986; UA003.003.070.00003 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 19, 1986; UA003.003.070.00004 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, January 21, 1987; UA003.003.070.00005 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 18, 1987; UA003.003.070.00006 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 18, 1987; UA003.003.070.00007 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 15, 1987; UA003.003.070.00008 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 15, 1987; UA003.003.070.00009 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 15, 1987; UA003.003.070.00010 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 15, 1987; UA003.003.070.00011 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 7, 1987; UA003.003.070.00012 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 8, 1987; UA003.003.070.00013 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 8, 1987; UA003.003.070.00014 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 8, 1987; UA003.003.070.00015 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 16, 1987; UA003.003.070.00016 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 16, 1987; UA003.003.070.00017 (Box 70)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 16, 1987; UA003.003.071.00001 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, September 16, 1987; UA003.003.071.00002 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 21, 1987; UA003.003.071.00003 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 13, 1987; UA003.003.071.00005 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, January 20, 1988; UA003.003.071.00006 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 17, 1988; UA003.003.071.00007 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, March 16, 1988; UA003.003.071.00008 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [1/2], UA003.003.071.00009 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [2/2], UA003.003.071.00010 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [1/2], UA003.003.071.00011 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [2/2], UA003.003.071.00012 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [1/2], UA003.003.071.00013 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 20, 1988 [2/2], UA003.003.071.00014 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 21, 1988; UA003.003.071.00015 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 19, 1988 [1/2], UA003.003.071.00016 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 21, 1988 [2/2], UA003.003.071.00017 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 21, 1988 [1/2], UA003.003.071.00018 (Box 71)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 21, 1988; UA003.003.072.00001 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, November 16, 1988; UA003.003.072.00002 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, February 15, 1989; UA003.003.072.00003 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 26, 1989 [1/2], UA003.003.072.00004 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 26, 1989 [2/2], UA003.003.072.00005 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 26, 1989 [1/3], UA003.003.072.00006 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 26, 1989 [2/3], UA003.003.072.00007 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, April 26, 1989 [3/3], UA003.003.072.00008 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 17, 1989 [1/3], UA003.003.072.00009 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 17, 1989 [2/3], UA003.003.072.00010 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, May 17, 1989 [3/3], UA003.003.072.00011 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 18, 1989 [1/2], UA003.003.072.00012 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, October 18, 1989 [2/2], UA003.003.072.00013 (Box 72)
    - Academic Affairs, November 15, 1989; UA003.003.073.00001 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, February 23, 1990; UA003.003.073.00002 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00003 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00004 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00005 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00006 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00007 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1990; UA003.003.073.00008 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, May 16, 1990; UA003.003.073.00009 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, May 16, 1990; UA003.003.073.00010 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, October 17, 1990; UA003.003.073.00011 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, October 17, 1990; UA003.003.073.00012 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, November 14, 1990; UA003.003.073.00013 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, June 8, 1991; UA003.003.073.00014 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, June 8, 1991; UA003.003.073.00015 (Box 73)
    - Academic Affairs, January 16, 1991; UA003.003.074.00001 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00002 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00003 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00004 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00005 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00006 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 17, 1991; UA003.003.074.00007 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, October 16, 1991; UA003.003.074.00008 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, October 16, 1991; UA003.003.074.00009 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, October 16, 1991; UA003.003.074.00010 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, November 1, 1991; UA003.003.074.00011 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, February 28, 1992; UA003.003.074.00012 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, February 28, 1992; UA003.003.074.00013 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, February 28, 1992; UA003.003.074.00014 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, February 28, 1992; UA003.003.074.00015 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.074.00016 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.074.00017 (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00001 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00002 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00003 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, April 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00004 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, May 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00005 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, May 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00006 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, May 15, 1992; UA003.003.075.00007 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, October 21, 1992; UA003.003.075.00008 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, October 21, 1992; UA003.003.075.00009 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, October 21, 1992; UA003.003.075.00010 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, November 6, 1992; UA003.003.075.00011 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, November 6, 1992; UA003.003.075.00012 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, February 26, 1993; UA003.003.075.00013 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, February 26, 1993; UA003.003.075.00014 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, April 21, 1993; UA003.003.075.00015 (Box 75)
    - Academic Affairs, April 21, 1993; UA003.003.076.00001 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, May 21, 1993; UA003.003.076.00002 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, May 21, 1993; UA003.003.076.00003 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, October 20, 1993; UA003.003.076.00004 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, October 20, 1993; UA003.003.076.00005 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, November 5, 1993; UA003.003.076.00006 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, November 5, 1993; UA003.003.076.00007 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, February 25, 1994; UA003.003.076.00008 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, April 28, 1994; UA003.003.076.00009 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, April 28, 1994; UA003.003.076.00010 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, May 20, 1994; UA003.003.076.00011 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, May 20, 1994; UA003.003.076.00012 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, November 4, 1994; UA003.003.076.00013 (Box 76)
    - Academic Affairs, September 22, 1994; UA003.003.077.00001 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, September 22, 1994; UA003.003.077.00002 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, September 22, 1994; UA003.003.077.00003 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, September 22, 1994; UA003.003.077.00004 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, February 10, 1995; UA003.003.077.00005 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, February 10, 1995; UA003.003.077.00006 (Box 77)
    - Acdemic Affairs, June 19, 1995; UA003.003.077.00007 (Box 77)
    - Acdemic Affairs, June 19, 1995; UA003.003.077.00008 (Box 77)
    - Acdemic Affairs, June 19, 1995; UA003.003.077.00009 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00010 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00011 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00012 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00013 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00014 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00015 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, April 20, 1995; UA003.003.077.00016 (Box 77)
    - Academic Affairs, February 9, 1996; UA003.003.078.00001 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 1, UA003.003.078.00002 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 2, UA003.003.078.00003 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 3, UA003.003.078.00004 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 4, UA003.003.078.00005 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 5, UA003.003.078.00006 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 18, 1996, part 6, UA003.003.078.00007 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, May 17, 1996, part 1, UA003.003.078.00008 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, May 17, 1996, part 2, UA003.003.078.00009 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, October 3, 1996, part 1, UA003.003.078.00010 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, October 3, 1996, part 2, UA003.003.078.00011 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, October 3, 1996, part 3, UA003.003.078.00012 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, October 3, 1996, part 4, UA003.003.078.00013 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, November 1, 1996; UA003.003.078.00014 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, February 7, 1997; UA003.003.078.00015 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 1, UA003.003.078.00016 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 2, UA003.003.078.00017 (Box 78)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 3, UA003.003.079.0001 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 4, UA003.003.079.0002 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 5, UA003.003.079.0003 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 24, 1997, Part 6, UA003.003.079.0004 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, May 16, 1997; UA003.003.079.0005 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, June 24, 1997; UA003.003.079.0006 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, September 18, 1997, part 1, UA003.003.079.0007 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, September 18, 1997, part 2, UA003.003.079.0008 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, September 18, 1997, part 3, UA003.003.079.0009 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, November 7, 1997; UA003.003.079.0010 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, February 6, 1998, part 1, UA003.003.079.0011 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, February 6, 1998, part 2, UA003.003.079.0012 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, March 12, 1998; UA003.003.079.0013 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 1, UA003.003.079.0014 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 2, UA003.003.079.0015 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 3, UA003.003.079.0016 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 4, UA003.003.079.0017 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 5, UA003.003.079.0018 (Box 79)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 6, UA003.003.080.0001 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 7, UA003.003.080.0002 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 23, 1998, part 8, UA003.003.080.0003 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, May 15, 1998, part 1, UA003.003.080.0004 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, May 15, 1998, part 2, UA003.003.080.0005 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, September 24, 1998, part 1, UA003.003.080.0006 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, September 24, 1998, part 2, UA003.003.080.0007 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, November 6, 1998; UA003.003.080.0008 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, February 5, 1999; UA003.003.080.0009 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 1, UA003.003.080.0010 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 2, UA003.003.080.0011 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 3, UA003.003.080.0012 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 4, UA003.003.080.0013 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 5, UA003.003.080.0014 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, April 22, 1999, part 6, UA003.003.080.0015 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, May 21, 1999, part 1, UA003.003.080.0016 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, May 21, 1999, part 2, UA003.003.080.0017 (Box 80)
    - Academic Affairs, September 23, 1999, part 1, UA003.003.080.0018 (Box 80)
    - September 23, 1999 part 2, UA003.003.081.00001 (Box 81)
    - November 6, 1999; UA003.003.081.00002 (Box 81)
    - February 11, 2000; UA003.003.081.00003 (Box 81)
    - April 18, 2000, part 1, UA003.003.081.00004 (Box 81)
    - April 18, 2000, part 2, UA003.003.081.00005 (Box 81)
    - April 18, 2000, part 3, UA003.003.081.00006 (Box 81)
    - April 18, 2000, part 4, UA003.003.081.00007 (Box 81)
    - April 18, 2000, part 5, UA003.003.081.00008 (Box 81)
    - May 19, 2000, part 1, UA003.003.081.00009 (Box 81)
    - May 19, 2000, part 2, UA003.003.081.00010 (Box 81)
    - February 10, 1996; UA003.003.083.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - May 18, 1996; UA003.003.083.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - November 2, 1996; UA003.003.083.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - November 27, 1996; UA003.003.083.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - January 7, 1997; UA003.003.083.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - February 8, 1997; UA003.003.083.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - February 8 to August 6, 1997 (Retreat committee), UA003.003.083.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - March 24, 1997; UA003.003.083.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - May 17, 1997; UA003.003.083.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - September 18, 1997; UA003.003.083.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - November 7, 1997, part 1, UA003.003.083.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - November 7, 1997, part 2, UA003.003.083.00012 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - February 7, 1998; UA003.003.083.00013 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - May 16, 1998, part 1, UA003.003.083.00014 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - May 16, 1998, part 2, UA003.003.083.00015 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - November 7, 1998; UA003.003.083.00016 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
    - Academic Affairs Working Papers, September 28, 1995 (1 of 4), UA003.003.100.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Academic Affairs Working Papers, September 28, 1995 (2 of 4), UA003.003.100.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Academic Affairs Working Papers, September 28, 1995 (3 of 4), UA003.003.100.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Academic Affairs Working Papers, September 28, 1995 (4 of 4), UA003.003.100.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Academic Affairs Working Papers, November 3, 1995; UA003.003.100.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Academic Affairs, 2005 -- 2006; UA003.003.127; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 127, Folder 1 - 11)
    - Academic Affairs, 2007 -- 2009; UA003.003.125; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 125, Folder 1 - 13)
    - Academic Affairs, 2007 -- 2010; UA003.003.126; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 126, Folder 1 - 18)
  - Academic affairs files, 2000-2016; UA003.003.00001; 1447 Digital Object(s); 2.98 Gigabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00003; 4 Digital Object(s); 5.92 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00004; 2 Digital Object(s); 1.2 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00005; 6 Digital Object(s); 5.51 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00006; 25 Digital Object(s); 49 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00007; 12 Digital Object(s); 11.6 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00008; 4 Digital Object(s); 3.26 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00009; 19 Digital Object(s); 55.7 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00010; 5 Digital Object(s); 4.71 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00011; 13 Digital Object(s); 49.5 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00012; 5 Digital Object(s); 7.09 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00013; 19 Digital Object(s); 59.4 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2017; UA003.003.00014; 12 Digital Object(s); 15.5 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2018; UA003.003.00015; 26 Digital Object(s); 49.6 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2018; UA003.003.00016; 9 Digital Object(s); 12.8 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2018; UA003.003.00017; 6 Digital Object(s); 5.21 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2018; UA003.003.00018; 27 Digital Object(s); 62.8 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs committee files, 2018; UA003.003.00019; 19 Digital Object(s); 18.8 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs Committee files, 2001-04-24; UA003.003.00020; 23 Digital Object(s); 21.73 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs Committee files, 2008-02-08; UA003.003.00021; 27 Digital Object(s); 35.83 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-07-26; UA003.003.00022; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.14 Megabytes
  - Academic Affairs Committee files, executive session, 2018-08-20; UA003.003.00023; 17 Digital Object(s); 63.58 Megabytes